{
    "subject": "resource/GoldenSource",
    "predicate": "ontology/keyPerson",
    "object": "resource/John_Eley",
    "human_readable": "The key person associated with GoldenSource is John Eley.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9631603956222534,
            "question": "Name a key individual involved with GoldenSource."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9563822150230408,
            "question": "Who is the key person associated with GoldenSource?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9151315093040466,
            "question": "Is there a connection between John Eley and GoldenSource?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9117011427879333,
            "question": "What is John Eley known for in relation to GoldenSource?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8786523342132568,
            "question": "Who is considered the main person associated with GoldenSource?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8558498620986938,
            "question": "What is John Eley's relationship to GoldenSource?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8511497974395752,
            "question": "What role does John Eley play in relation to GoldenSource?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.79188472032547,
            "question": "Who is a prominent figure linked to the company GoldenSource?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7661576271057129,
            "question": "Can you tell me about someone important involved with GoldenSource?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7222219109535217,
            "question": "Is there a well-known individual connected to GoldenSource?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The key person associated with GoldenSource is John Eley.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1547_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about someone important involved with GoldenSource?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1547_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is a prominent figure linked to the company GoldenSource?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1547_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role does John Eley play in relation to GoldenSource?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1547_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1547_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1547_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1547_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1547_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1547_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1547_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1547_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1547_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1547_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1547_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found the following:\n\n* The company \"GoldenSource\" is mentioned multiple times, and its CEO is indeed \"John Eley\".\n* There are no contradictory statements about John Eley being associated with GoldenSource.\n\nTherefore, my response is:\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that John Eley is a key person associated with GoldenSource. Specifically, multiple documents mention John Eley as the CEO of GoldenSource, indicating his significant role in the company."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}